snapvillage.com 2009-04-16

# SnapVillage - Privacy Policy

At SnapVillage, we understand and respect your concern about the privacy of any information you supply while at our Site. We believe that knowledge is the key to monitoring and protecting how your information is used on the Internet. This statement sets forth SnapVillage's Privacy Policy and describes the practice SnapVillage follows with respect to all visitors to this Site. If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement please do not hesitate in contacting us. Email your questions to the Contact Us page. 

SnapVillage’s Privacy Policy applies to use of this Site, and its terms and conditions are made part of this Agreement by reference. You understand that any message or information sent to the Site may be viewed or intercepted by third parties, even if there is a special notice that the information (e.g., financial information) is encrypted. Except as limited by the Privacy Policy, you agree that SnapVillage may contact you regarding the Site, your User account, or activity on the Site, via the contact information you have provided.

A. Children  
B. Personal Information  
C. Content Referral  
D. Profile Information  
E. Automatically Collected Information  
F. Use of Service Providers  
G. Change of Address or Contact Information  
H. Security  
I. Cookies  
J. E-mail  
K. Surveys and Contests  
L. Transfers to Other Jurisdictions  
M. Discussion Threads  
N. Links  
O. Changes of SnapVillage' Online Privacy Policy  
P. Legal Disclaimer

A. Children. Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use this Site unsupervised and we ask that children do not register for an account or submit any personal information to us. By using this site unsupervised, and/or registering for an account, you warrant that you are 18 years of age or older. 

 B. Personal Information. SnapVillage collects certain personal information from users of this Site. Users are required to provide certain personal information in order to access images, and authorized users must provide certain contact and account information such as name, email address, billing address, and phone number in order to access and download images. SnapVillage may use certain account information such as credit card number and company information of authorized users to conduct credit inquiries. SnapVillage uses this information for internal purposes (to process your order and any invoices, to maintain or update your SnapVillage account, or, unless you have indicated that you do not wish to receive such information, to send you updates about special offers, new services, special promotions, and noteworthy news and events). SnapVillage does not sell or rent information about its users to third parties.   
[top]

C. Content Referral. If you use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, or inviting a friend to view images you have selected at SnapVillage, we will ask you for the friend's name and email address. SnapVillage will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. SnapVillage does not retain this information.

[top]

D. Profile Information. Your public and private profile information in the registration form is used by SnapVillage to create personalized content, services, and advertising on the SnapVillage Site. SnapVillage also requests, at your option, that you create a public profile that allows you to share information about yourself with other users of the Site. Unless you indicate otherwise, SnapVillage may also profile your Site activity in order to accurately track your account and provide you with SnapVillage products and services that correspond to your interests. SnapVillage may also compile data in aggregate form so that we may better understand the users that are visiting our site. For example, we may produce reports on the most popular search terms by collecting general search term data based on individual searches. Aggregate data is anonymous and does not contain any personal information that identifies a user. 

[top]

E. Automatically Collected Information. As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses may be tied to personally identifiable information to segregate customer types for analytical purposes. When you use the Contact Us page, email addresses are not automatically collected but may be optionally submitted by user. SnapVillage will use this email address and any personal information collected for the purpose of responding to the user's request. 

[top]

F. Use of Service Providers. We occasionally hire or partner with other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as hosting the Site, managing and handling the processing and delivery of mailings (both email and postal mail), providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.   
[top]

G. Change of Address or Contact Information. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete inaccuracies in your information by making the change by making those changes on your My Account page or contacting us through the Contact Us page. Your request will be processed and implemented within thirty (30) days.   
[top]

H. Security. SnapVillage has a number of operational functions in place to protect the confidentiality of personal information. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access that are located in secured facilities. SnapVillage' employees are trained and kept up-to-date on our security procedures. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can contact us through our Contact Us page. We and our payment vendors use SSL encryption technologies to transmit sensitive information such as a credit card number to our servers. However, perfect security on the Internet does not exist, and SnapVillage does not warrant that its Site is impenetrable or invulnerable to hackers.   
[top]

I. Cookies. When you visit the SnapVillage Site, SnapVillage sends your computer a cookie, which is a small file that resides on your computer's hard drive and contains non-personally identifiable information about the user. Cookies only identify the user's computer. Cookies allow SnapVillage to make its Site more useful by storing information about your preferences. For example, SnapVillage will send your computer a cookie to maintain default settings. You can set your browser's options not to accept cookies, but this may prevent you from accessing all of the features of the SnapVillage Site. 

Additionally, this Site uses clear GIFs, or pixel tags, provided by our adserving company to help manage our online advertising. These clear GIFs provide our adserving company with the ability to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site. This allows us to learn which banner ads bring users to our Site. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable (it does not include your name, address, telephone number, or email address). For more information about our adserving company or your option to restrict the use of this anonymous information, please contact us via the Contact Us page. 

SnapVillage uses a third party to assist in managing the licensing of our images. This third party uses clear GIFs, a tiny 1x1 pixel GIF, to digitally watermark our images, in both a visible and invisible manner. When you   
license Content from us, the visible watermark is then removed from the image, however, in certain lower resolution images, an invisible watermark may remain, allowing SnapVillage and the third party to track certain usage of such images on the Internet.

[top]

J. E-mail. SnapVillage does not rent or sell e-mail lists. SnapVillage may send you e-mail to notify you about your recent order; this will be sent to the e-mail address you provide to SnapVillage. SnapVillage offers its members the choice to not receive e-mails or updates about special benefits, promotions, or offers from SnapVillage. If you no longer wish to receive these updates, or you wish to unsubscribe from SnapVillage membership you may change your Communication Preferences via your My Account page, or by writing to us using the Contact Us Page. 

[top]

K. Surveys and Contests. Participation in surveys or contests on the SnapVillage Site is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose personal information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for the purposes of monitoring or improving the use of the SnapVillage Site. 

[top]

L. Transfers to Other Jurisdictions. Use of your information in accordance with this online privacy policy may from time to time involve sharing you information with SnapVillage Parties and SnapVillage’s service providers. This may include the transfer of your information to other countries, including countries which do not afford the same level of protection as may be available in your home country. SnapVillage will only transfer your information to such countries where it obtains adequate assurances from the third party as to the level of protection it will afford your data. SnapVillage and its associated companies in the United States of America abide by the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.  
[top]

M. Discussion Threads. If you use SnapVillage's Community Forum or blog discussion threads, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these discussion threads.   
[top]  
  
N. Links. Please be aware that the SnapVillage Site may contain links to other web sites that are covered by their own privacy policies. SnapVillage is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and we encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site. We recommend that our users read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

[top]

O. Changes of SnapVillage' Online Privacy Policy   
SnapVillage reserves the right to change our online privacy policy. However, we shall not do so without posting those changes on the SnapVillage Site. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you via email or by posting a prominent notice on our Site thirty (30) days prior to implementing the change. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner.   
[top]

P. Legal Disclaimer. We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or to comply with a legal process served on our Site.   
[top]

If you have any questions about SnapVillage's privacy policy or concerns about personal information you have supplied to SnapVillage, please contact SnapVillage Customer Service via the Contact Us page. You may also write to us at the address listed below:

SnapVillage Limited   
Attn: Matsack Trust Limited   
70 Sir John Rogerson’s Quay   
Dublin 2   
Ireland  
[top]
